[Music]
[Música]
Okay guys,
bueno chavales ayer
yesterday an event happened to close 2020
ayer sucedió un hecho para cerrar 2020
which the art of carranza welcome to
el cual the art of carranza bienvenida a
thank you very much which you did not
muchísimas gracias el cual ustedes no os
expect at all I am not going to
esperabais para nada yo no os voy a
fool you the habeas corpus this week stay in
engañar los hábeas la semana quédate en
it so they do not steal your roulette wheels so we
it así sus no te roban las ruletas así
leave you all the roulette wheel of the south no
le dejamos toda la ruleta del sur no
well I will not think I already tell you that I am not saying
bueno no pensaré ya os digo que no digo
anything for sure but I will think about it
nada seguro pero me lo voy a pensar
skylar thank you very much I am
skylar muchísimas gracias
not going to lie okay I already knew
no voy a mentir vale yo ya lo sabía
obviously you know we are the
evidentemente ya sabéis somos el amigo
mutual friend I am a member with two channels one
en común soy miembro con dos canales un
male rita and another one so white that's why
macho rita y otro la tan blanca por es
you are too good to be
que tú eres demasiado bueno para ser
true hey hey bought other things for
verdad oye oye comprado otras cosas para
the mic you see this it is called anti
el micro esto lo veis se llama anti
rebound
rebotes
javi on vimeo it supports 4k and it is better than
javi por vimeo soporta 4k y va mejor que
winning
ganar
if we stay we stay here if we
si nos quedamos nos quedamos aquí si nos
stay we stay here okay
quedamos nos quedamos aquí vale
buying this is also another kind
el comprar esto también es otra especie
of racket
de raqueta
I don't know why all these things are not
yo no sé por qué todas estas cosas no la
sold with the mic the mic that costs
venden con el micro el micro que vale
close to 200 bucks damn they can also
cerca de 200 pavos [__] puedan también
wifey give me the racket give me the
la esposita dame la raqueta el dame lo
other stuff there's more stuff I can't
otro se halla más cosas no le puedo
put the microphone on it so it can be seen like
poner el micrófono para que se vea de la
crazy okay so it can be seen like crazy
[__] vale para que se vea de la [__]
ok no more stuff don't put anything and nothing guys
ok ya más cosas no poner y nada chavales
because of what happened yesterday well a little surprise I
por lo que pasó ayer pues una sorpresita
already told you there would be a surprise I see there were there were
ya os dije que habría sorpresa ya veo
more surprises it's to end
había había más sorpresas es para acabar
the year powerful powerful powerful armando
el año potente potente potente armando
welcome to the command cube one person there's
bienvenidos al mando cubo una persona me
another surprise I mean this one was powerful
hay otra sorpresa o sea ésta era potente
the disaster welcome I already told you
lo desastre bienvenida ya os lo dije
just how many videos are coming
sólo cuánto de vídeos se vienen cosas
very powerful things before the end of the year for
muy potentes antes de acabar el año para
dad dad there's another one
papá papá queda otra
maybe two but there's a very very very
tal vez dos pero hay una
very powerful
muy muy muy muy potente
okay very very very very powerful
vale muy muy muy muy potente
when I say something very powerful it's like
cuando yo digo algo muy potente es como
yesterday's
lo de ayer
session or yesterday
de sesión o lo de ayer
we expected it and not at all the
nos lo esperaba y para nada los los
pear trees not at all
perales para nada
tic tac thank you very much
tic tac que muchísimas gracias
welcome
bienvenido
well here's another thing powerful powerful
pues aquí hay otra cosa potente potente
powerful but tomorrow is tomorrow the 30th no I
potente pero ya mañana es mañana 30 no
already have my doubts that there will be
ya tengo mis dudas de que vaya a dar
time for that to happen before the
tiempo a que eso suceda antes de que
end of the year because it would have to be
acabe el año porque tendría que ser
tomorrow or the day after
mañana o pasado
and it's going to be very rushed okay
y va a estar muy precipitado vale
surely it's going to be  early
seguramente ya va a ser a principios de
January but at the very beginning, like
enero pero muy al principio o sea en
the first week or so okay there's
plan la primera semana o así vale queda
another piece of news that's really really really powerful really really powerful
otra noticia muy muy muy potente muy muy
that's going to bring us two or three
potente que nos va a traer dos o tres
really really powerful videos okay but anyway what happened
vídeos muy muy potentes vale pero bueno
yesterday we have to admit that it was
lo de ayer tenemos que reconocer que fue
really good no longer lonely January
buenísimo no ya enero solitario
welcome thank you very much yesterday
bienvenido muchísimas gracias lo de ayer
was a before and after making yesterday
fue un antes y un después hacer de ayer
youtube history
fue historia de youtube
yesterday was youtube history ok i'm
lo de ayer fue historia de youtube ok
not going to lie i'm a mutual friend you already
no voy a mentir soy el amigo en común ya
know no no it didn't catch me by surprise I
lo sabéis no no me pilló de sorpresa ya
had already in fact I think we
os había de hecho creo que hablar esto
talked about this before Christmas Eve so
lo hablamos antes de nochebuena o sea
this was a long time ago
esto hace ya un montón de tiempo o sea
or something like that and so okay they
por ver una semana o algo así y así a
spend them between they've met
vale los pasan entre que han quedado
to record and such well it's happened okay but
para grabar y tal pues ha dado vale pero
to me it seemed wonderful okay now
a mí me pareció maravilloso vale ahora
let's take a look at the cries
vamos a echar un vistazo a los llantos
of course this has sat badly with a
por por supuesto esto ha sentado mal a
lot of people victoria here no welcome to thank you
mucha gente victoria acá no bienvenida a
very much this has sat badly with
muchísimas gracias esto ha sentado mal a
a lot of people and there are a lot of people
muchísima gente y hay mucha gente
crying raging kicking dog
llorando rabiando pataleando perro
Cristiano welcome although you already
cristiano bienvenido aunque ya lo eras
were a member your name sounds
ya lo era miembro me suena tu nombre
very familiar
muchísimo
by the way javi do you think I'll become and
por cierto javi crees que me haré y
antonia will be raging about begin
antonia estarán rabiando por lo de begin
thoughtful face to some
cara pensativa a alguna información
privileged information of yours haha ​​ps you are the
privilegiada de las tuyas jaja pd eres
best
el mejor
seeing raging I don't know what I know for
aver rabiando no lo sé yo lo que sé
sure is that seeing her sitting seeing
seguro es que viendo la sentado viendo
her sitting okay because because [ __ ]
la sentada vale porque porque [__]
because they tried to get along
porque ellas intentaban llevarse bien
with life I mean them
con vida osea ellas
antonia put a lot of
antonia le ponía muchos comentarios
nice comments to virgin in her photo you know thing
bonitos a virgin en su foto sabe cosa
that to me seemed
que a mí me parecía
hypocritical or whatever to call it okay
entonces hipócrita o como llamarlo vale
because antonia has spoken badly to me about
porque a mí antonia me ha hablado mal de
these people I have I have the
esta gente yo tengo tengo la
conversation speaking badly about these people
conversación hablando mal de esta gente
and I when because he was manuel that a
y yo cuando porque él fue manuel que un
follower who was always giving me
seguidor que me estaban dando siempre
screenshots of everything of everything there were some
capturas de todo de todo todo hubo unas
times that he sent me consider the mind
veces que me mandó consideran la mente
no screenshot that antonia putting the
no captura de que la antonia poniendo el
message avellino oh oh how pretty that I don't
mensaje avellino ay ay qué guapa que no
know what that I don't know how much and it's like day
sé qué que no sé cuánto y es como día
ma'am please if sanz sent me
señora por favor si a mí me mandaba sanz
and they spoke badly to me about these people and he
y me hablaban mal de esta gente y me
told me that you knew very bad things about these
decía que sabías cosas muy malas de esta
people
gente
well he will not have sat it because
bien no lo habrá sentado porque haber
virgin is very powerful
virgen es muy potente
apart from in the couple of someone very
aparte en la pareja de alguien muy
powerful of  24 welcome
potente de 24 bienvenidos
related to jordi while what's coming get
relacionado a jordi while lo que viene
wet they don't have a very powerful vision very
mójate no tienen muy potente visión muy
powerful and suddenly they see that
potente y que de repente se vean que
auro ida does a collaboration
auro ida hace una colaboración
with dallas
con dallas
with how bad they feel about everything
con lo mal que le sientan a ella todo lo
that is good for dallas
que es bueno para dallas
or in other words they base their criteria on following
o sea que basan su criterio en seguir a
someone not following someone is that they
alguien no seguir a alguien es que le
throw [ __ ] at them a psychologist comes out
tiren [__] la sale una psicóloga
making a thread about dallas follows her
haciéndole un hilo a dallas la sigue la
follows her in the retweets and the whole roll
sigue en la retuitea y todo el rollo
okay they must have
vale
felt lied to because I lived in
les habrá sentado mentido porque viví en
the video that came out saying that they didn't believe
el vídeo salido diciendo que no creían
the things that they said basically he
las cosas que ellas decían básicamente
didn't mention them but he said something like
no las mencionó pero dijo algo así como
well I don't want to involve third
que bueno no quiero meter a terceras
parties but I don't believe that he is an
personas pero no me creo ni que sea un
animal abuser or an abuser
maltratador de animales ni maltratador
or anything like that or I mean he
ni nada por el estilo o sea
must have seen things and he must have come to the
habrá visto cosas y habrá llegado a la
conclusion that he doesn't believe it
conclusión de que no se lo cree
okay then of course as they must have
vale entonces pues claro como les habrá
felt bad bad obviously they must have
sentado mal mal evidentemente les habrá
felt bad because what they want
sentado mal porque ellas lo que quieren
are allies okay she says they are
son aliados vale ella lo dicen son
allies you see the mother on twitter and
aliados tú ves a la madre en twitter y
the mother all day on twitter her
la madre todo el día en twitter su
job her mission is le  I give a like I
trabajo su misión es le pongo un like le
give a comment to this journalist I
pongo un comentario a este periodista le
give this to twitter or ha ha ha boom
pongo a este twitter o ja ja ja boom
hervé I know it's not the time but
hervé yo sé que no es el momento pero
I'm not a mod yet I
aún no soy mod
love you lollipop face in love lollipop
te amo piruleta cara enamorada piruleta
to truth the mot to hydro please
a verdad le mot a hidro por favor
moderators the strange thing in my opinion is that
moderadores lo raro en mi opinión es que
wish mocho hasn't deleted the
wish mocho no haya borrado todavía el
video yet, the reviews are like this I
vídeo de así estar las review me
wonder why
pregunto por qué
out of pride and pride and he's not going to
por orgullo y por orgullo y no lo va a
delete it until he has the obligation
borrar hasta que no tenga la obligación
to delete what I hope will be soon
de borrar lo que espero que sea pronto
very soon okay I hope it's soon
muy pronto vale espero que sea pronto
look me sincerely talking about the subject
mira yo sinceramente hablando del tema
of willie when finishing with what if
de willie cuando terminando con lo de
we sit down honey and antonio let's
que si nos sentamos la miel y antonio a
see there are many people criticizing what would
ver hay mucha gente criticando que
antonia send they have stopped following
enviaría antonia han dejado de seguir a
live on this occasion I see it logical
vivir en esta ocasión yo lo veo lógico
because if beijing in the live wave la
porque si beijing en el directo onda la
in the video goes to it gives it to understand that we don't
en el vídeo anda la da a entender que no
believe them is normal
se las creemos es normal
okay it didn't let me be the bank and as a
vale no me dejaba ser el banco y como
Christmas present they let me now haha
regalo de navidad me dejan ahora jaja
ah okay I'm from Argentina well look from
ah vale soy de argentina pues mira de
Argentina that one can become a member thank you very much
argentina esa puede hacer miembro muchas
dog
gracias perro
is normal that you stop following her  I mean it
es normal que la dejes de seguir o sea
's normal because Virginia has been
es normal porque virginia hacía como una
following them for like a week and if
semana que las debo de seguir y si
on top of that she said in the video that they do
encima a vivir en el vídeo ha dicho que
n't believe the things she says, well it's
no se creen las cosas de ella pues es
normal that I've helped them continue knowing it's not
normal que las ayudado a seguir saber no
like other times when they just stop
es como otras veces que simplemente
following someone because they know how to
dejan de seguir a alguien porque saben
tell what has happened too no
contar las que ha pasado también no
but thanks for not having made him
pero gracias por no le habrá hecho
obviously such a powerful person
evidentemente una persona tan potente
making peace with Dallas that a lot a
haciendo las paces con dallas que mucho
lot of hatred towards Dallas and being
mucho del odio hacia dallas y de quedar
singled out in the community for the fight
señalado en la comunidad por la pelea
with this group, now this is where it all started
con este grupo ya con esto empezó todo
this is where it all started if Dallas had
con esto empezó todo si dallas nunca se
never fought with Aura a play and instead of fighting with Aurum play they would have gotten along surely to this day Dallas would not have gone through many of the things that he has gone through because everything grew there what happens is that Raúl is very powerful wind michu also in his time now people do not
también en su época ahora la gente no la
support him but in his day people ate his
apoya pero en su día la gente le comía
ass and much more not being able to then as a
el culo y mucho más no poder entonces a
result of that fight well okay then
raíz de esa pelea pues tal vale entonces
now make peace let
pues que ahora hagan la paz se vaya la
people go fall taking off the blindfold and
gente vaya cayendo quitándose la venda y
falling the dada comes to him well that's it
cayendo le viene el dadá pues eso a
They won't have been amused they
ellas no le habrá hecho gracia ellas
want it to be like Dallas
quieren que en tal que el dallas el
ruins his life and that it's the end and
arruina la vida y que sea su final y
all that you understand and nothing well they
todo eso me entendéis y nada pues ellos
want allies okay it's what you live
quieren aliados vale es lo que viváis
being the mother stays all day I
siendo la madre se queda todo día
give him a layer to a challenge and to Ruben
le doy un layer a un reto y a rubén
Sanchez okay then Ruben Sanchez more
sánchez vale que luego rubén sánchez más
the favor of posting the news I do
el favor de poner las noticias le hago
hahaha to this twitter or I give it a like
jajaja a este twitter o le doy un like
you to see how it goes I once said
you to verse cómo va yo en su día dije
that I did something similar to
que hacía como algo parecido a
public relations and he whatever and
relaciones públicas y él tal cual sea y
all this is to look for contacts for
todo esto es para buscar contactos para
his battle so that then hey I
su batalla para que luego pues oye me
need you to publish this news
hace falta que publiques estas noticias
Ruben Sanchez Ruben Sanchez you take him out to
rubén sánchez rubén sánchez lo sacas a
see things were going anyway
ver cosas iban en fin
then open the tamale of course
entonces le abras el tamal por supuesto
but it
pero
is what there is what there is the truth
es lo que hay lo que hay es la verdad
has a path and people realize
tiene un camino y la gente se da cuenta
things and that's it
de las cosas y ya está
regarding the issue of wing michu let's see my
respecto al tema de wing michu a ver mi
opinion would also sit down that there was
opinión sentaría también que hubiera
unity between Dallas and all the others with
unión entre dallas y todos los demás con
whom he had his differences what happened
los que tuvo sus diferencias lo que pasó
with begin could  be a huge step of
con begin podría ser un paso enorme
course well I'm going to give my opinion on wind and
claro bueno voy a opinar de wind y
brag I already said what a huge step I
chulear ya digo lo del paso enorme lo
say in michu any normal person
digo en michu cualquier persona normal
dude or rather any person like
tío o sea cualquier persona como pude
me in my day does it to me
ser yo en su día se hace a mí me
and I see that the other person is
denuncia y veo que la otra persona tiene
right and that I have the odds against me
razón y que tengo las de perder
and now
y ya hay que
knowing everything that is known that
sabiéndose todo lo que se sabe que el
dallas doesn't see all the things that have been
dallas no ve todas las cosas que se han
said and these things
dicho y estas cosas
any person would say dallas
cualquier persona diría dallas
let's reach an agreement and not go
vamos a llegar a un acuerdo y no vayamos
to trial I mean because the complaint
a juicio o sea porque la denuncia nos
bets us from yesterday the complaint has I don't
apuesta de ayer la denuncia tiene yo no
know but I think the complaint is
sé pero yo creo que la denuncia está
placed in the video of buen bicho it was in
puesta en el vídeo de buen [__] fue en
2017 I don't know exactly what date
2017 no sé exactamente en qué fecha
I could give the complaint but maybe it
podría darle a la denuncia pero capaz y
was around 2018
fue por 2018
zawiya had time he decided chiapas
zawiya tenía tiempo ha decidido chiapas
that we are going to be so many years and not years
que vamos a estar tantos años y no años
but now when the trial is to
sino que ahora cuando sea el juicio
resort to more time you know I mean the thing is
recurrir a más tiempo sabe o sea la cosa
that he didn't have the need to get into
que no tenía la necesidad de meterse en
that he
eso
is a youtuber who didn't have the need to
es un youtuber que no tenía la necesidad
have gotten into that
de haberse metido en eso
and to have continued with his content and
y haber seguido con su contenido y
surely water and michu would do better  and I would
seguramente agua y michu le iría mejor y
have more credibility if I hadn't
tendría más credibilidad si no hubiera
made that video Hector Torre welcome
hecho ese vídeo héctor torre bienvenido
then any person Freddy Javi
entonces cualquier persona freddy javi
my girlfriend only gets jealous of type of make me
mi novia sólo se cela de type de hazme
mod lollipop
mod piruleta
be careful with Freddy I'm dangerous just
cuidadito de freddy que soy peligroso es
kidding send him a kiss from me
broma mandarle un beso de mi parte
react to the Dallas
reacciona al vídeo de dallas de
psychology video with grace I
psicología con gracia
don't know what video that is but today we have
no sé qué vídeo ese pero hoy tenemos
finished and we have
terminado y tenemos
the thing the question what
la cosa la cuestión lo que decía
any normal person was saying goes and says oh
cualquier persona normal coge y dice ah
right I was wrong with you dude
verdad las me equivoqué contigo tío
let's reach an agreement
vamos a llegar a un acuerdo
come on how much is against the lawyer de
venga cuanto está contra el abogado de
la Vega I'll pay you and I make a video and I
la vega yo te lo pago y hago vídeo y
say that this is not how it is that I was wrong
digo que esto no es así que me equivoque
that punk bites in stern and it's fixed but he
que pique punk en popa y se arregla pero
doesn't do it and this is already stubbornness
no lo hace y esto ya es cabezonería
because 80% of the internet already knows that
porque ya el 80% de internet sabe que
everything that is said in that video is a lie
todo lo que se dice en ese vídeo mentira
worth 80 but it's already stubbornness you know
vale el 80 pero ya es cabezonería sabes
seat and let's see
seat y vamos a ver
grab some tea
coge té
or I mean I think it's for two reasons one
o sea yo creo que es por dos motivos una
of two or because the people
de dos o porque la gente que tiene a su
around him don't allow it
alrededor no se lo permite
and they want to reach an agreement they wouldn't
y nos quieren llegar a un acuerdo no se
allow it or already out of pride but already the
lo permitirían o ya por orgullo pero ya
pride thing  it seems because he is
lo del orgullo me parece porque es que
truly lost it is that I believe
está perdido de verdad es que yo creo
that in that trial
que ese juicio
I could be wrong it would be best if he
ya me puedo equivocar sería lo mejor que
had a judge who did not give it
le toque un juez que no le dé
importance
importancia
but I know that there are serious accusations in
pero yo es que hay acusaciones graves en
that video that is there no longer no longer
ese vídeo eso sea ahí ya no ya no le
call someone an [ __ ] an idiot I do
llames a alguien [__] tonto del
not know what it is they are
culo no sé qué es que se le están
calling him an abuser they are
llamando maltratador se les está
calling him an animal abuser he
llamando maltratador de animales
puts the photo of Cristina Bernal as if she
pone la foto de cristina bernal como si
were under 16 knowing that she is not
fuera menor de 16 sabiendo que no lo es
knowing I do not know it seems enormous to me it seems enormously enormously to
saber ya no sé me parece muchísimo me
me it would seem
parece muchísimo muchísimo me parecería
extremely lucky if he did not lose that
muchísima suerte que no perdiera ese
trial the truth is I see it almost impossible
juicio la verdad lo veo casi imposible
very improbable in fact
muy improbable de hecho
and I already believe that the people who are
y ya es que yo creo que la gente que
around him do not allow him to see
tiene alrededor pues no le permite a ver
fix things with Dallas at the
arreglar las cosas con dallas en su
time as he has done to euros as he has
momento como ha hecho a euros como ha
done
hecho
and now and as such we divide it a
y ahora y como tal lo dividimos un paso
big step of course guys so I look
grande pues claro tíos así que yo mira
if they are going to fight okay because Dallas
si van a pelear vale porque el dallas
now as we were had exploded the
ahora como estábamos había explotado el
Beijing issue not only of the three
tema de beijing no sólo de los tres
former and he is ready the king of that was
antiguos y está listo el rey de ese era
the Basque law there is a video telling everything
la ley vasca está un vídeo contando todo
that  It happened to you in the past and what was
lo que le pasó en el pasado y cuál era
the weak part and the weak part and that
la parte débil y la parte débil y que
was it, well, retweet, you're going to support
era pues retuitea va a apoyar a las
things towards your partner, some insults,
cosas hacia su pareja algunos insultos
threats, anyway, okay, then go
amenazas en fin vale entonces dale
ahead, make a video and I said, look,
arriba hace un vídeo y dije mira
sincerely, I am two people that
sinceramente soy dos personas que
I appreciate, I would not like for her to enter into
aprecio no me gustaría que entrará en
a war and that is not what I do not care
una guerra y ya no es lo que me da igual
if she stays, you fight about you, there
que si se quede pelea usted de usted
is more of how you have fought many
haya más de cómo se han peleado muchas
times, people that I know, it is time to
veces personas que conozco ya está por
be here and react to the videos, the
estar aquí y reaccionar a los vídeos los
comments, I will give my opinion, that's it,
comentarios daré mi opinión ya está ya
no, that is, I am two people that you
no eso es que soy dos personas
can talk, you can solve
que podéis hablar que podéis solucionar
things, you
las cosas
can solve things because I
podéis solucionar la cosa porque yo me
talk to her, give her an account
hablo con ella le das una cuenta de
lately, well, I talk a lot
últimamente pues hablo bastante
and I know that it would be with you and it has
y yo sé que sería contigo y no tiene
nothing and you with her,
nada y tú con ella
Tarragona, with her, you talk about things
tarragona con ella habla en las cosas
and it is solved and it will be the best for
y se soluciona y va a ser lo mejor para
everything, the best for everyone and I say, well,
todo lo mejor para todos y digo bueno
Sara, Sara, at the moment she said, of
sara sara en el momento dijo por
course, let's talk, would you say that the
supuesto vamos a hablar dirias que la
bomb to come is that in Beijing,
bomba por venir es que lo de beijing
yes, of course, of course, much
sí claro por supuesto por supuesto mucho
more, the
más
shooting room than if he spoke at the
sala del tiroteo que si él habló al
beginning like  that they argued a bit
principio como que discutieron un poco
until like all the people who have
hasta que como todas las personas que
had problems at the beginning speak
han tenido problemas al principio habla
for your voice
por tu voz
and they spoke and super cool and it seemed like
y hablaron y super guay y me ha parecido
a wonderful video what they have done an
un vídeo maravilloso lo que han hecho un
example that things can be
ejemplo de que las cosas se pueden
fixed
arreglar
an example that you are not - for
un ejemplo de que no eres - por pedir
apologizing because he does not apologize and vai
disculpas porque no pide disculpas y vai
that it is not going to be valuable
que no lo va a ser valiosa
the same surprises us in 2021 and we have
lo mismo nos sorprende de 2021 y tenemos
ibai apologizing too but it is not
a ibai disculpándose también pero no lo
going to be like
va a ser
that as a probability if the dean video
así como probabilidad si el vídeo deán
was 40 k and how much do you think
fue 40 k y cuánto crees que podría
the video could cost wish mocho they
salirle el vídeo a wish mocho
are different complaints they are
son denuncias diferentes son denuncias
different complaints also from what I
diferente además por lo que tengo
understand I think that we michu loss
entendido creo que a we michu lass
posted several I do not know I am not sure
puesto varias no lo sé no estoy seguro
okay but they are different things they are
vale pero son diferentes cosas son
different processes they have nothing to do
diferentes procesos no tienen que ver
with each other I do not know it seems like an
una cosa con la otra no sé parece una
average it does not pass an average the truth is the
media no se pasa una media la verdad el
topic of today I suck me there are other things
tema de hoy me chupo hay otras cosas
behind there are contracts or in other words the vitality
detrás hay contratos o sea la vitalidad
that the video of good michu had was
que tuvo el vídeo de buen michu fue
super fat the video several for 20
súper gorda el vídeo varias por 20
million has lost contracts with
millones ha perdido contratos con
companies and cause as a result of that video, in other
empresas y cause a raíz de ese vídeo o
words, it must be valued a lot there  that
sea hay que valorarlo muchísimo hay que
value many things is worth it then
valorar muchísimas cosas vale entonces
Carles welcome
carles bienvenido
Liszt thank you very much thank you very much
liszt muchísimas gracias muchísimas
welcome
gracias bienvenidos
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
basically I don't know what you think about
básicamente a mí no sé qué pensáis de
you all I think that 98% of the people
ustedes yo creo que el 98% de la gente
on the internet are graded with that video the
en internet sale grado con ese vídeo la
surprised okay
sorprendido vale
but there is a 2% of the people that there is not
pero hay un 2% de la gente que no hay un
2% of the people said that things burn them
2% de la gente dijo que le arden las
okay that they hate this
cosas vale que le tienen odio a este
kid and that's it we will tell them and they
chaval y ya está que les diremos y lo
have to hate him because the dalai must be
tienen que odiar porque el dalai hay que
hated okay here I was asking you to can
odiar lo vale aquí os pedía que podéis
answer this tweet with the cries of
contestar este tweet con los llantos de
the people for Dallas Vicky
la gente por lo de dallas vicky
ah well this regarding this gives him away to
ah bueno esto referente a lo delata para
post this tweet
poner este tuit
because if he doesn't have a lopera I am very brave
porque si no tiene lopera me valentísimo
for this VPN compound okay
por este compuesto vpn vale
don't watch the video Fandila 'el fandi'
no vean el vídeo fándila 'el fandi'
gay neighborhood don't watch the video they get
barrio gay no vean el vídeo que le dan
visits to the egg unemployed and on top of that he
visitas al huevo desempleado y encima
makes money
gana plata
don't watch the video they get visits to the
no veas el vídeo que le dan visitas al
unemployed website
desempleado
I don't like Sara but
a mí no me cae bien sara pero webó
can you please  stop minimizing her
pueden por favor dejar de minimizarla a
girlfriend and I say done being stand by
la novia de y digo hecho siendo stand de
one is enough it's not that difficult to say
a uno basta no es tan difícil decir
debate with sara virgin there is no one I also don't
debate con sara virgin no hay tampoco
think I'll see it to give views to dallas the
pienso verlo para darle views a dallas
girlfriend thing let's see I'll explain it you have to
lo de novia de a ver yo lo explico hay
put it to visit the same okay you have to
que ponerlo para visitar a mismo vale
put it for visits it's not the
hay que ponerlo para las visitas no es
same
lo mismo no poner lo que no ponerlo hay
not to put what as not to put it you have to put it for visits it's not done to belittle her or anything but let's see because she's known Miguel thank you very much to be absurd it wouldn't be absurd not to value her less or anything but it would be absurd to say that she is not known because on the 9 d auro I don't know it does
conoce porque en la 9 d auro no sé a mí
n't seem like an offense to me or anything
no me parece ninguna ofensa ni nada
okay go [ __ ] yourself
vale
this [ __ ]
vete a tomar por culo esta [__] no
had nothing to do with you but not the
tenía nada que ver contigo pero no el
victim child the victim child has to
niño víctima el niño víctima se tiene
get in until they screw you I
que meter hasta que te jodan
hope it's the last
ojalá sea el último
good video I hope it's the last die
buen vídeo ojalá sea el último muere
dallas I
dallas
saw a friend from my area today
he visto hoy a una amiga de mi área
post this post
poner esto
this image
poner esta imagen
and I will become aracne okay to the city to whom
y me haré aracne vale a ciudad a la que
this image was posted and I will become she
le ha puesto esta imagen y me haré le ha
responded to the tweet telling her with a  little
respondido al tuit diciéndole con una
face
carita
not unemployed you have me up to my
no desempleado me tienes hasta los
ovaries
ovarios
what would it cost the sick man from Dallas to at
que le costaba al enfermo de dallas por
least put his nickname put videos
lo menos poner su nick poner vídeos
now if in the end he profits by calling her
ahora si al final se lucra por llamarla
the girlfriend of god how annoying if you put it
a la novia de dios qué rabia si lo pones
today or if you put it remove it
hoy o si lo pones quitar
and I also put it aurum
y yo lo pongo también novia de aurum
play's girlfriend and in my friend she is not
play y en mi colega ella no sea
Dallas he is the opportunist and pathetic of
dallas es el oportunista y patético de
all youtube
todo youtube
when are you going to stop minimizing
cuando vas a dejar de minimizar a la
people like the girlfriend of or the friend of
gente como la novia de o el amigo de
flaco stop looking for visits by putting the
flaco deja de buscar visitas poniendo el
name of a recognized person in the
nombre de una persona reconocida en el
title
título
well well why don't you deactivate
bueno bueno porque no desactivas
deactivate both
desactiven los dos
hopefully it's the last one to this one from high
ojalá sea el último a este desde alto
just like they have put it repeated to me
igual que me lo han puesto repetido
when a casting is done the [ __ ]
cuando se hace un casting el [__]
what is a casting is
que es un casting
something of ghosts ghost and what is it is
es algo de fantasmas ghost y que es es
something of ghosts no no
algo de fantasmas no
delete it
no borrarlo
said people go on imbecile profit you
dijo la gente dale imbécil lucra te de
call someone I'm not going to see
llamar a alguien no voy a ver
but why have people burned
pero por qué la gente se ha arde
because people are burned because Dallas will
porque la gente se arde porque dallas
do things with people god is
harán las cosas con la gente dios se
amazed
admira
look at the tweet that I  they have sent by
mirar el tweet que me han mandado por
email that he has deleted it he has deleted it
email que lo ha borrado lo ha borrado
but come on now that he hits you all day
pero vamos ahora que te pega todo el día
every controversy that Dallas has you post a
cada polémica que tiene dallas pones un
tweet because they send it to me you know I don't
tweet porque me lo mandan sabe yo no me
have a block on me but people send me they
tiene bloqueo pero la gente me manda me
still send me to this day and yes I
mandan todavía a día de hoy y si me
imagine that they didn't send me everything if
imagino que no me lo mandaron todo si
a psychologist makes a thread for her
una psicóloga le le hace un hilo
she shares it if she does post a tweet
ella lo comparte si da la pone un tweet
from Elliot Page she posts something god of
de elliot page ésta pone algo dios de
all they post something he's the kilo the other
todos ponen algo está el kilo el otro
guy get over it since you have
tío superarlo ya que ustedes nos ha
done nothing to us
hecho nada
Richard Guzmán welcome
richard guzmán bienvenido
and get over it is that in fact
y superarlo es que de hecho le había
you had done it to him so that he would whitewash
hecho ustedes a él para que blanqueará
bullish and harassers it would be should be
bullish y acosadores sería debería ser
a custom to stop in 2020
una costumbre que dejar en 2020
whitewashing bullies and harassers and you
blanquear a bully y acosadores y te lo
are being aracne who had a blog or
estáis siendo aracne que tenía un blog o
a website okay a blog dedicated to
una página web vale un blog dedicado a
Dallas to the life of Dallas okay he
dallas a la vida de dallas vale que lo
was updating it every week every
iba actualizando cada semana cada
controversy in Dallas well he's already been
polémica de dallas pues ya lo lleva
updating it there on the blog
actualizando ahí en el blog
god
dios
and Asia live for 7 hours with the
y asia directo de 7 horas con los
surfers [ __ ] man
surfers [__] tío
anyway daily forum and let it live
en fin foro cotidiano y lo dejara vivir
let's start reading you sandra
vamos a empezar a leerte sandra
welcome from the heart thank you very much
bienvenida a corazón muchísimas gracias
publish in the video you
publica en el vídeo
know and tell me javi is needed in the
ya sabéis y dime javi hace falta en el
dallas mercury a cup that puts up to
mercurio de dallas una taza que ponga al
date about you I would buy it x well
día de ti yo lo compraría x de bueno
when the website store opens we will
cuando abra la tienda de la página web
put it okay hey remind you that
ya lo pondremos vale oye recordaros que
the website is really crazy
la página web es una auténtica burrada
the support it is having okay look
el apoyo que está teniendo vale mirad
how well it works look at all the
qué bien que funciona mirar todos los
topics it has all its little things okay
temas que tiene todas sus cositas vale
the page is really cool from
la página es una auténtica pasada desde
here like the simple the a
aquí le como el simple el a
there it goes okay that you don't see the page that
ahí va vale que no veas la página que se
has been set up it already has two thousand 173
ha montado tiene ya dos mil 173 personas
registered people ok
registradas ok
two thousand 173 registered people one
dos mil 173 personas registradas un
million 250 thousand visits I do
millón 250 mil visitas
n't know how many days to make the page I
no sé cuántos días hacer esta la página
think it was like two or three weeks
creo que era como dos o tres semanas
wow
guau
they registered that it is totally free and
registraron que es totalmente gratis y
the page is amazing okay it
la página es una pasada vale
never ceases to amaze me 2020 okay
no me deja de sorprender el 2020 vale ya
you know that the daily forum is like a
sabéis que el foro cotidiano es como una
notification it works better than the
notificación funciona mejor que la
youtube bell on the click  from
campanita de youtube en el click de
twitter the part that I have commented is missing
twitter falta la parte que he comentado
okay this is talking about workers
vale esto están hablando de trabajadores
apologize to the anonymous people and not to
discúlpate con la gente anónima y no con
who will report benefits to you literally
quién te va a reportar beneficios
literally
literalmente literalmente
what happens with the sun camera or in the
qué pasa con la cámara de sol o en la
camera
cámara
to clean the camera
para limpiar la cámara
orange movement
movimiento naranja
the future is in your hands movement
el futuro está en tus manos movimiento
nothing
nada
[Music] we
[Música]
have to see
hay que ver
that point is d
ese punto es d
that with this point it is true let's
que con este punto es verdad
see
a ver
where that point comes from that
de donde ese punto
point is something
ese punto es algo
well here is life
pues aquí está la vida
here it is now to put the
aquí está ahora al meterle la
update but well
actualización pero bueno
literally it will be done in the video he
literalmente se hará en el vídeo se
apologizes again because he had already
disculpa por otra vez porque ya se había
apologized in the past but
disculpado en el pasado pero
literally it is now he apologizes for
literalmente es ahora se disculpa por
the tweets from those years okay
por los tweets desde aquellos años vale
so watching the video here before
así que mirando el vídeo aquí antes de
criticizing okay good first time
criticar vale buena primera vez
commenting on this thread in my opinion
comentando en este hilo en mi opinión
that anger was more to demonstrate that
ese enojo fue más para demostrar el que
if he defends his girlfriend as an example or
si defiende a su novia como ejemplo o
rather this of a victimizer I am going
sea esto de victimario lo voy a tener
to have to see it because there are people who say that surely at the moment what I caught okay surely at the moment it bothered him because the truth is I have seen around there what I say about Mario and unpleasant the truth is a little unfortunate surely at
es un poco desafortunado seguramente en
the moment they got upset  with him but
el momento se molestaron con él pero
then they could wanted to be like
luego puedan quería ser como que no pasa
nothing's wrong what's up
nada que bromas volverá a jugar
wind michu will play again interact with aura and sala
interactuar wind michu con aura y sala
after this video well there wouldn't be
después de este vídeo pues no tendría
anything it wouldn't have to affect okay what
nada no tendría por qué afectar vale lo
happens is that sara and now a play are
que pasa es que sara y ahora un play son
two people who since they don't need
dos personas que como no necesitan de
anyone well they don't care okay there are a lot of
nadie pues les da igual vale hay mucha
people I remember especially in the past
gente me acuerdo sobre todo en el pasado
that for fear that win michu wouldn't get
que por miedo a que win michu no se
upset they wouldn't interact with dallas
molestará no interactuaban con dallas
in my opinion putting boyfriend to de I think it
en mi opinión poner novio a de creo que
helps to easily identify the person
sirve para identificar a la persona con
and know that it's not a nobody and it
facilidad y saber que no es un nadie y
's not always for objetiv and carl for
no siempre es para objetiv y carl por
example I didn't know who
ejemplo yo no sabía quién
beijing was until they said that she's
era beijing hasta que dijeron que es la
aurum's girlfriend imagine if I
novia de aurum que imaginaros que yo
were yellow melo's boyfriend this
fuera el novio de yellow melo
has come out again this this this
otra vez ha salido a esto
where the hell does it come from
esto de esto de dónde [__] sale
again it has come out
otra vez ha salido
but it's here it's not in the camera
pero está aquí no está en la cámara
lying in front of the camera
echada delante de la cámara
the mind the camera in the frame life
la mente la cámara en el cuadro vida
to the camera in the frame well we
a la cámara en el cuadro
change the sizes let's see
pues cambiamos los tamaños a ver
hey what a son of a [ __ ] no let's see
oye que el hijo de [__] no haber
or rather it's something that's in front but we don't
o sea es algo que está adelante pero no
know what let's see what things are in
sabemos el que a ver qué cosas hay
front of this no  I believe this I don't believe this
delante esto no creo esto no creo esto
no
no
something that is in front of the camera let's
algo que está delante de la cámara vamos
see
a ver
now it has become it's not here let's
ahora se ha vuelto no está aquí
see today what we have changed has been
a ver hoy lo que hemos cambiado ha sido
this so it has to have to do with
esto así que tiene que tener que ver con
this but I'm not moving and no let's
esto pero no me estoy moviendo y no
see
a ver
look at it
miralo
the lots
los lots
well nothing said down here so that it annoys
pues nada dijo por aquí abajo para que
us besides
nos dé por culo además no están saliendo
the others are not coming out no
los otros no
and if an ad appears well we already
y si aparece algún anuncio pues ya lo
know
sabemos
what things I didn't know was going around
qué cosas no sabía que iba por ahí
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
as I was saying there were many people in
como iba diciendo había mucha gente en
the past who did not want to interact with
el pasado que no querían interactuar con
Dallas in case Wii Michu got upset about
dallas por si wii michu se molestaba por
it I promise that there were youtubers who
lo prometo que había youtuber que me
told me that literally
decían eso literalmente
and now not even Sara well they are people who don't care they do
y ahora ni sara pues son personas que
n't have to go after
les da igual no tienen que ir detrás de
anyone they don't have to please please
nadie no tienen que agradar agradar a
anyone
nadie
they are them and you are good to them always
ellos son ellos y les vais bien siempre
do what they do and they don't care and if they
hagan lo que hagan y les da igual y si
have to talk to one and the other they
tienen que hablarse con uno y con otro
will do it that if said well he will
lo van a hacer que si bien dicho va a
want to play with them after it is done well
querer jugar con ellos después de hecho
he will see who is interested in playing
pues él verá al que le interesa jugar
with them in fact
con ellos a él de hecho
my one rule of the camera or I already the thing about
my one regla de la cámara o yo ya lo de
Ivan as a joke
iván como un chiste
joint image wash of rooms
lavada de imagen conjunta de salas
why do they put room
porque ponen sala
because they are so ridiculous and sara would
porque son así de ridículas y sara
never have imagined it a little
jamás lo hubiese imaginado una
question sara ingrid get along well
preguntita sara ingrid se llevan bien
after this I don't believe it
pues después de esto no lo creo
until now they follow each other on twitter
hasta el momento se siguen en twitter
okay but ingrid is probably going to get
vale pero ingrid seguramente se va a
mad at her and unfollow her
enfadar con ella y la bajar de seguir
for sure because what if you have apologized
segurísimo porque y si te has disculpado
to my abuser and have said that he is not
con mi maltratador y has dicho que no es
an abuser it
un maltratador
is obvious that he is more inclined to continue and
es obvio que inclina más a seguir y
play dumb I am sure I
hacerse la pelada seguro
need bigger capital letters
necesito mayúsculas más grandes
I like that she lowers herself with dallas tomorrow I will
me gusta que se rebaje con dallas mañana
see it when I have a little time it does
lo veo cuando tengo un ratito
not seem to me that it is lowering herself to lower
no me parece que sea rebajarse a
herself it is that why why should she lower herself for
rebajarse a ella ella rebajarse por
asking for an apology and then the other one who
pedir disculpa y entonces el otro que se
lowers himself because he accepts the apology
rebaja porque acepta las disculpas
because the other was made a
porque al otro le hicieron de las
sailorritas I have recorded a video
marineritas se le he grabado un vídeo
for the main channel that is in the
para el canal principal que está en la
morning okay and there I do more or less a
mañana vale y ahí hago más o menos un
review of everything that happened in the
repasito de todo lo que pasó en el
past of these people and others between the
pasado de esta gente y demás entre las
rules of the fabric
reglas de la tela
I am in a state of shock like  I would say aura I've been
estoy en estado de shock como diría aura
freaking out with this plot tweets for a while I
llevo un rato flipando con este plot
must say that it doesn't really
tweets debo decir que en realidad no me
surprise me both have the same audience both
sorprende ambos tienen el mismo público
win they
salen ganando ambos
already see it as a business thing I
ya lo ven como algo de negocios yo
don't like hey well let's be even let's
no como oye pues vamos a estar en paz
show that we can fix
vamos a demostrar que podemos arreglar
things that there are no hard feelings they don't
las cosas que no existen rencores no lo
see it as a business thing and besides both
ven como algo de negocio y aparte ambos
have the same audience
tienen el mismo público
statistics to these people
estadísticas a esta gente
what statistics that these people share
qué estadística que esta gente comparten
the same audience no way
el mismo público ni de coña
the crossover of the two animes has
el crossover de los dos animes se ha
happened
producido
now yes it's canceled and now it's still
ahora sí que cancelada y ahora sigue
canceled okay
cancelada vale
yes it was already half canceled because of tweets
si ya tenía medio cancelada por tweets
from 2013
del 2013
now it's still canceled
ahora ya sigue cancelada
for talking to you with dallas that is
por hablarte con dallas eso es
unforgivable apologize now yes it
imperdonable pedirle disculpa ahora sí
's canceled
que cancelada
and it gives me a little cricket the video is that it
y me da un poco de cricket el vídeo es
is very strange all salty seems to
que es muy raro todo salado parece
emphasize what has been done it is an offense it is not
recalcar se ha hecho es una ofensa no se
supposed to not seem to emphasize every minute
supone no parece recalcar a cada minuto
how bad sara is and she
lo mala que es sara y esta pide
apologizes but justifying herself for everything
disculpas pero justificándose por todo
I fix her pc but you
yo le arregló el pc pero vosotros os
become members I'm waiting to see there
hacéis miembros estoy esperando a ver
are 2,700  there are 1200 people here right now
hay 2.700 personas hay ahora mismo aquí
in the chat who are not
en el chat 1200 personas que no son
members
miembros
I think it would be really nice to end the
yo creo que sería muy bonito acabar el
year
año
with all of you here now
con que todos los que estáis aquí
members at once and we're just looking at
hay miembros de golpe y estamos viendo
the forum
el foro
anymore you couldn't ask for guys at the
más no se podría pedir chavales al
price of a piece of gum you get it at the price
precio de un chicle lo tenéis al precio
of a piece of gum and on top of that you can set it to be
de un chicle y encima lo podéis poner a
charged through your
que se cobre mediante la factura del
cell phone or cesc bill which you're not going to notice
móvil o cesc que no lo vais día notar
guys or even write down to
chavales ni anotar
write right now the chat
a escribir ahora mismo el chat
becoming a member
haciéndose miembro
okay while we look at the Bolivian forum
vale mientras que vemos el foro
this video only serves to encourage the
este vídeo sólo sirve para alentar la
variety of Dallas salt and Sara and for
variedad de sal de dallas y sara y que
Sara to apologize in quotes for what
sara pida disculpas entre comillas por
is on twitter saying some
lo que es en twitter decir cosas
pretty interesting things analyze that the
bastante interesantes análise que el
friend that these two have in common
amigo que tienen en común estos dos les
told them that they won't trust x friend because
dijo que no confiarán en x amiga porque
then they go talking bad about her on the forum
luego van hablando mal de ella en foro
well that's not exactly what he's
bueno no es eso exactamente lo que lo
saying okay what he's saying is that he won't
que dice vale lo que dice es que no
trust people who get along with
confiara en gente que se lleve bien con
people from the forum it's
gente del foro
not normal it's not normal I mean I wouldn't
ya no es normal no es normal o sea yo no
get along with any youtube
me llevaría con ningún youtube
gora and  Thank you so much for listening to me,
gora y muchísimas gracias por hacerme
welcome, welcome. I wouldn't
caso bienvenido bienvenido yo no me
get along with anyone who got along
llevaría bien con nadie que se llevara
with half the forum. It seems like
bien con medio foro austeros parece que
that's about being a good friend and then you
eso de ser buen compañero que luego tú
go hehe haha ​​with the other YouTubers
vayas jiji jaja con los otros youtubers
when those YouTubers are having a
cuando esos youtuber los están pasando
really bad time in the everyday forum and it turns out
muy mal por el foro cotidiano y resulta
that you get along with half the forum
que tú te llevas con medio foro
or it seems like that's about being a good friend. I wouldn't
o parece eso de buen compañero yo no me
get along with any YouTuber
llevaría con ningún youtube
if I found out that that YouTuber gets along
si me entero que ese youtuber se lleva
with people from the forum and the truth is there are
bien con gente del foro y la verdad hay
people who talked to Sara or
gente que se hablaba con sara o se
followed Zara who get along with
seguía con zara que se lleva bien con
half the forum but well who take photos
medio foro pero bien que se hace fotos
with people from the forum and that and that they
con la gente del foro y que y que se
have groups of jokes with people from the
tienen grupos de guasa con la gente del
forum. Man, you know that there are people who are
foro hombre ya sabes que hay gente está
literally, you know that there are many
literalmente sabes que hay muchos
influencers, there are many influencers, man
influencer hay muchas influencer tío
Sara and not even Terra Rocío Camacho,
sara y ni terra rocío camacho
there are many influencers who are having a
hay muchos influencias que lo están
terrible time with the [ __ ] shitty forum,
pasando fatal con el [__] foro de [__]
okay, and you go and you're friends with people from the
vale y vas tú y eres amigo de gente del
forum, I was more like with half the forum, okay
foro tenía más bien con medio foro vale
because because it's convenient for you to
porque porque a ti te conviene para
filter  information on the forum
filtrar información en el foro
like what happened to me they said the street
como me pasó a mí que dijeron la calle
where I live that my dog ​​was bought well
donde vivo que mi perro era comprado
I wouldn't get along with anyone
pues yo no me llevaría bien con nadie
so of course not straight welcome thank you
así que claro no lo recto bienvenido
very much there is
muchísimas gracias
an imposter
hay un impostor
Javier thank you very much that's what he did
javier muchísimas gracias eso mismo hizo
with the video explaining about the
con el vídeo explicando lo de las
stones a while ago in a good way
piedras hace un tiempo en plan de buenas
but the [ __ ] dropping machine doesn't
pero la máquina de soltar [__] no la
let it not even as a joke
deja ni de broma
elche doesn't give stitches without thread it
elche no da puntadas sin hilo
's that I'm sure that dallas had a
es que estoy segura de que dallas tenía
capture of all of Sara's twitter with
captura de todo el twitter de sara con
what it said at that time there were surely
lo que ponía en esa época seguro que
very bad things and they have made this
había cosas muy chunga y han hecho esta
kind of deal in which both
especie de trato en el que los dos salen
benefit let's
beneficiados
see is that in any case you have already taken
a ver es que de todas formas ya habéis
out everything that put Sara in 2013 we have
sacado todo lo que ponía a sara en 2013
been analyzing it toxic
lo hemos estado analizando toxic
welcome welcome thank you very much
bienvenido bienvenido muchísimas gracias
to all of you who are listening to me
a todos los que me estáis haciendo caso
today we would break them seriously it is
hoy en los romperíamos en serio es de
really we would break it or rather of 1,700
verdad lo romperíamos o sea de 1.700
people here there are 1,200 who
personas que aquí hay 1200 que todavía
are not members yet
no son miembros
if you all do it you
si todos lo hacéis
noticed that he lived I would stay watching the
fijaron que vivió me quedaría viendo el
forum in  I leave your hands in
foro en vuestras manos lo dejo en
your hands they believe in their minds
vuestras manos ellas creen en su mente
that even if all of
que aunque salieran todos los tweets de
Sara's tweets from 2013 came out they would already cancel her and
sara del año 2013 ya la cancelarían y
ruin her career they don't understand that
arruinaría su carrera no se enteran que
no, no, that these are things from 2013 girls I
no que no que son cosas del 2013 chicas
already did it in the video that I made of each
ya lo hice en el vídeo que hice de todas
and every one of you we make you read
y cada una de ustedes os ponemos a leer
whatsapp
whatsapp
the forum message tweets or anything
el mensaje del foro tweets o cualquier
that I wrote in 2013 and surely there
cosa que haya escrito en 2013 y seguro
are much worse
que son mucho peores
things video ati or nvidia the triumph of
cosas video ati o nvidia el triunfo de
the people and that things go well for people and that they
la gente y que a la gente le vaya bien y
make peace with dallas you can't
que haga las paces con dallas no podéis
superior okay
superior vale
at the beginning no but throughout 2013 they
al principio no pero a lo largo de 2013
ingratiated themselves
se congraciaron
and she says sorry really big
y la pone diciendo lo siento bien grande
one thing that always does it
una cosa que siempre lo hace
well we already know that they were like that
bueno ya sabemos que eran así
and stalker because she wasn't okay
y acosadora porque no estaba bien
with herself poor
consigo misma pobrecilla
Nancy stalker I'm freaking out
nancy acosadora yo estoy flipando
unicorns of the prairies I
unicornios de las praderas me ha
loved the part where the free room
encantado la parte en la que sala libre
because they put salar because you put it
porque ponen salar porque lo pones al
backwards
revés
what an [ __ ] only a forum member
qué [__] solo forera
what an [ __ ]
qué [__]
says it  of the photos of corpses and
dice lo de las fotos de cadáveres y sale
says that's what was popular on
diciendo que es lo que se llevaba en
Twitter she told him about the photos of a
twitter le ha dicho de las fotos de bebé
dead baby and says that it's impossible that
muerto y sale diciendo que imposible que
she's never done that to which Dallas
ella jamás ha hecho eso a lo que dallas
responded that he saw it and she
ha respondido que él lo vio y ella
accuses herself with a story even in this
acusándose con una milonga hasta en este
video she tries to lie saying that she
vídeo intenta mentir diciendo que todos
took them all from public police accounts
los saco de cuentas públicas de la
sara my love in Victorian times there
sara cariño mío en la época victoriana
were photos of corpses because
había fotos de cadáveres porque las
photos were very expensive
fotos eran carísima
and people took photos with their deceased
y la gente hacia foto con sus fallecidos
to have thanks to Adrian to have
para tener gracias a adrián para tener
a last memory of it
un último recuerdo de ello
this woman here and really Adrian thank you
esta mujer aquí y de verdad adrià
so much churri is here
muchísimas gracias churri está
thank you so much to all of you who
muchísimas gracias a todos los que nos
are listening to us and have looked
estáis haciendo caso y habéis mirado
have looked at how to become members and
habéis mirado cómo hacer los miembros y
have seen that it's nothing it's
habéis visto que no es nada es
just a matter of hitting the join button pim
simplemente darle al botón de unirse pim
pam pum take candy oliveira heat up
pam pum toma lacasitos oliveira calienta
that's coming out
que sale
oliveira has been hot for 10
oliveira está caliente desde hace 10
days and not with this topic but with other
días y no con este tema sino con otros
topics that have not yet come out and will come out
temas que todavía no han salido y saldrá
oliveira not to stop oliveira not to stop today
oliveira no para oliveira no para hoy
today I had a debate that has been
hoy he tenido un debate que ha sido
history
historia
leo mega welcome  Thank you so much
leo mega bienvenido muchísimas gracias
Leo Vega today's debate is
leo vega el debate de hoy es historia de
internet history too
internet también
where is the debate
dónde está el debate
go ocs thank you so much I appreciate
dale ocs muchísimas gracias te agradezco
the heart this debate this is internet history
el corazón este debate esto es historia
we have had albertito on this channel
hemos tenido albertito en este canal
okay hey albertito put me in a
vale oie albertito me ha puesto en un
tweet okay I said it before but I'll say it
tweet vale lo he dicho antes pero lo
again albertito put me in
vuelvo a decir albertito me ha puesto en
a tweet that he doesn't want to do the second
un tuit que no quiere hacer la segunda
part after he promised we have to
parte después de que lo ha prometido
ask him please there has to be a
tenemos que pedirle por favor que tiene
second part because we have
que haber segunda parte porque nos hemos
left many things in the inkwell
dejado muchísimas cosas en el tintero
but many many things in the
pero muchísimas muchísimas cosas en el
inkwell
tintero
baltasar welcome the king of salsa
baltasar bienvenido el rey del salsero
well and many things that you don't know okay
bueno y muchas cosas que no sabéis vale
but without salt if you knew
pero sin sal si supierais
javi the other time you did direcon
javi la otra vez que hiciste direcon
adrià and cripto they mentioned seva
adrià y cripto mencionaron a seva
izquierdo please don't hang out with him he
izquierdo por favor no te juntes con él
is crazy and now he is
está mal de la cabeza y ahora se
involved in a case of femicide and those who
involucró en un caso de femicidio ya los
rented to the murderer who is his
que le arrendaba al asesino que es su
friend and where he hid the girl who she
amigo y donde escondió a la niña
is do
de quién es
they intend to link me with
tienen intención de relacionarme con
anyone new
nadie nuevo
if you knew if you knew the one  people who
si supieras si supieras la de gente que
contact me family I can't count
me contacta familiar no puedo contar
but if you knew how many important people
pero si supieras la de gente importante
contact me and I can't talk
que me contacta y no puedo hablar
adrián carbonell welcome welcome
adrián carbonell bienvenido bienvenido
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey it will be
oye oye oye oye oye oye oye oye oye oye
fulfilled and the 1200
se cumplirá y se harán miembros las 1200
people who are left to become members will become kids
personas que faltan por hacerse chavales
and I'll give you a minty peek hey I'm a
y os doy un pico minty oye yo soy un
vinti peek like albertito's it's that
pico vinti como el de albertito es que
I know that many would pay for my peek I
yo sé que muchos pagarías por mi pico
lied it's
mintió
going to be funny how
va a ser gracioso cómo se justifican
all these who mentioned to me what
todos estos que me mencionaban lo que
Saleh had done justify themselves now that she herself has recognized it Victor that's going to be funny I don't understand it's going to be funny what is going to be funny Victor Agustín Palavecino Xavi Maria member if they unban my other main account here in this channel there is no one banned I have already
aquí en este canal no hay nadie baneado
said it many times I
ya lo he dicho muchas veces
don't understand I mean I have never said that at
no entiendo o sea yo nunca he dicho que
that time I would not post a certain tweet in fact
esa hora no pusiera cierto tuit de hecho
before I protested those who have it have
antes de que proteste ya quienes tengan
said that in their time I followed
ha dicho haber yo en su tiempo seguía
Sara to Ingrid that  include something like that
sara a ingrid que incluyera por el
since there are a lot of people here who
estilo e ya que hay mucha gente que aquí
weren't talking about Ingrid but and like that
no estaba hablando de ingrid pero que y
Christopher thank you very much and like that
christopher muchas gracias y por el
with these people it's really funny to me that
con esta gente me hace mucha gracia que
no one is mentioning her more welcome
nadie la está mencionando más bienvenido
guys it would be the best I really
chavales sería la [__] de verdad lo
say it it
digo
would be the best my friend he Javier he
sería la [__] mi pana él javier él
Alberto that's a great character don't
alberto ese es un personajazo no me
tell me don't tell me I don't believe it hey
digas no me digas que no me lo creo oye
but the second part has to come out yes
pero la segunda parte tiene que salir sí
or yes
o sí
the second part has to be yes or yes like that
la segunda parte tiene que ser sí o sí
well it will be your thing it depends on what you have
así pues será cosa tuya depende de lo
put whatever but here there is
que hayas puesto lo que sea pero aquí no
nothing very serious so become a
hay nada muy en serio así que hazte
member
miembro
already made a 23 minute reaction video
ya hizo una vídeo reacción de 23 minutos
ha ha ha ha ha
ja ja ja ja ja
lunatic thank you very much queen
lunática muchísimas gracias reina
that thanks to stores at 23 minutes it
que gracias a tiendas a 23 minutos no
wasn't the reaction it was an hour
era la reacción era de una hora
23 minutes ago okay year cheer up
hace 23 minutos vale año ánimo
thank you very much king
muchísimas gracias rey
pure afternoon
puro la tarde
pure tan it's not letting me become a
puro la tan no me está dejando ser
member help steven let's see it's super
miembro ayuda steven a ver es súper
easy you just have to hit the
fácil sólo tenéis que darle al botón de
join button and I and put the option I
unirse y yo y poner la opción os lo
recommend you put the option of the
recomiendo poner la opción de lo de la
mobile bill  it's the best because it
factura del móvil es lo mejor porque lo
comes with the cell phone bill and you don't even
pone con la factura del móvil y es que
realize that they're spending you 50
ni te enteras que te están gastando 50
cents more a month
céntimos más al mes
albertito would have to be crazy for
tendría que estar loco albertito para
that the man couldn't care less when he convinced him to
ese le da igual al hombre al convencerlo
come grace thank
de que venga grace muchísimas gracias
you so much you are so pretty gay really thank you so much hahahahaha after watching the video two opposing theories come to mind one it is known what authority they made peace and they get along therefore da la and sara must have done the same thing they have agreed to mutual whitening in which both
blanqueamiento mutuo en el que ambos
benefit
salen beneficiados
dallas is not that bad and sara will be she is
dallas no es tan malo y sara estará está
sorry about everything that's
arrepentida de todo
how things are sara no longer
es que las cosas son así sara ya no le
represents her her tweets and dallas are not
representa sus tweets y dallas no son
the things that are said to her
las cosas que se le dicen
what is the problem what a turn of
cuál es el problema menudo giro de
events cousins ​​I don't know what
acontecimientos primas no sé qué opináis
you think but I think that sara has been
vosotros pero creo que sara ha estado
more than correct and dallas too I have
más que correcta y dallas también la he
even seen her regretful ashamed of having
visto incluso arrepentida avergonzada de
had this dark phase let's see I
haber tenido esta etapa oscura a ver me
imagine it must be hard to
imagino que tiene que ser duro admitir
publicly admit all that [ __ ] I think
públicamente toda esa [__]
the forum has had a lot to
creo que el foro ha tenido bastante que
do with these apologies haha ​​for the
ver en estas disculpas jaja por la parte
dallas part I sincerely believe that win
de dallas sinceramente creo que win
michi mieres are more expelled
michi mieres están más expulsados
after this video
después de este vídeo
because you are taken to delay that look at it
pues estás llevado a delay que la mirad
loe they have already fixed the comment that has been
loe ya fijaron el comentario que ha
posted so respectful so sensible because I
puesto tan respetuoso tan sensato pues
put the dislike that you
la puesto dislike
cannot comment on the forum
eso no se puede opinar en el foro por
please this is a lot of text piece of a
favor esto es muchísimo texto pedazo
novel mister lonely
novela mister lonely
thank you very much
muchísimas gracias
brod report albertito it has done
brod denuncia al albertito ha hecho
a lot of [ __ ] much needed pending we have
mucha mrd mucha falta pendiente nos han
left topics in the inkwell I would pass it
quedado temas en el tintero lo pasaría
suddenly it has escaped there comes a
de repente se ha escapado ya llega un
time of the debate I'm
momento del debate
going I move less I want to talk more
me voy me mueve menos quiero hablar más
and no no
y que no que no
and it came out shortened in an hour although there are
y salido acortado en una hora aunque hay
many things to talk about and he said
muchísimas cosas por hablar y ha dicho
tomorrow the second part and he sent me a
mañana la segunda parte y me mandó
message saying that we should not
mensaje diciendo que no hay que
convince him to do the second
convencerlo de que hagamos la segunda
part and clarify everything because there are
parte y aclaremos todo porque se han
many things that I have here in
quedado muchas cosas que tengo aquí en
the inkwell although there are many things
el tintero aunque hay muchísimas cosas
in the inkwell
en el tintero
efe the most scared that I wanted to stay
efe el más asustado que me quería quedar
keifer kiefer rosado welcome mica
keifer kiefer rosado bienvenido mica
thank you very much for throwing that
muchísimas gracias por tirarme esa la
face at me really no  there's nothing that makes me
cara de verdad no hay nada que me dé más
happier than you saying those things to my face I
gusto que me diréis esas cosas a la cara
think I have to announce a day
creo que tengo que poner un día un poco
earlier to the ceo this video internet history
antes al ceo este vídeo historia de
sara making a video apologizing to
sara haciendo un vídeo disculpándose con
the most hated being on youtube they were referring
el ser más odiado de youtube se referían
to wisin and with the interested people
a wisin y con lo de la gente interesada
no I don't think so I think that comment
no no lo creo yo creo que ese comentario
helps as much as by someone like in
ayuda tanto como por alguien como en
general
general
I think it
yo creo
passed by here to remember the date on which the
pasó por aquí para recordar la fecha en
best debate 2020 is published without a
la que se publica mejor debate 2020 sin
doubt I have peed myself laughing badly written
duda me he meado de la risa mal escrito
many youtube privately to
muchísimos youtube por privado para
tell me that they were watching the debate and
decirme que estaban viendo el debate y
for the third but really seriously there are
para el tercero pero de verdad en serio
many things left in the
han quedado muchísimas cosas en el
inkwell that I would like the second part
tintero que me gustaría la segunda parte
well in fact I would not have liked if a
bueno que de hecho no me hubiera gustado
second part was necessary I
que hiciera falta segunda parte me
would have liked to finish the debate or rather
hubiera gustado terminar el debate o sea
that they would have given
que se hubieran dado
my god as I have had the mobile
dios mío como tengo el móvil
1 year already as a member
1 añito ya de miembro
forex thank you very much honey
forex muchísimas gracias cariño
thank you very much
muchísimas gracias
my mother on the mobile the others are
madre mía en el móvil los demás
exhausted
reventada
the income model
el modelo de renta
wanted to see how many views the
quería ver cuántas visitas lleva el
debate with albertito has
debate con albertito
subscribers a lot thank you very much
suscriptores un montón muchísimas
ryan  read at the top thanks
ryan lee en su cima gracias
incredible incredible the debate incredible
increíble increíble el debate increíble
the debate how it goes
el debate cómo va
but I insist done we don't need the
pero insisto hecho no hace falta la
second part
segunda parte
we need the second part because I
nos hace falta la segunda parte porque
mean there are so many
o sea que hay muchísimas cosas
important things but for my taste okay
importantes pero para mi gusto vale
pink palette how pretty you are that although
paleta rosa qué guapa eres que si bien
in that photo thank you very much also it is
en esa foto muchísimas gracias además
done churri it is I mean her laughter at
está hecho churri está o sea sus risas a
a quite important level
un nivel bastante importante
I like well envious comments I'm going
me gusta bien comentarios envidiosos voy
to leave the forum for a bit now and maybe we'll continue
a dejar un poco el foro ya y tal vez
reading it tomorrow because the small
sigamos mañana leyéndolo porque me está
print is causing me a bit of eyesight
causando un poco la vista de la letra
Valeria I've been here for many hours
pequeña valeria llevo muchas horas aquí
on the PC so surely with the forum we'll
en el pc así que seguramente con el foro
continue tomorrow and me what is this is
sigamos mañana y yo esto qué es
in this warehouse Esther Expósito
está en este depósito esther expósito
and they put her in the body of the monkeys a
y la ponen en el cuerpo de los monos
beauty wait she cracked up in the middle
a un bellezón espera se rajó en medio
of the live each one rolling with
del directo cada revolviéndose de la
laughter wow suddenly it's him I entered a
risa wow de repente es el entro del
panic and he threw the skype
pánico y se tiró el skype
suddenly in a panic and Shapiro
de repente dentro del pánico y shapiro
okay well I'm going to leave the force here I'm going
vale pues voy a dejar el force aquí voy
to know around here on page 177 and
a saber por aquí en la página 177 y
tomorrow we read all the other pages
mañana leíamos todas las demás páginas
okay this thing was simply to
vale este trasto era simplemente para
review a bit all the  cries of the
repasar un poco todos los lloros de la
angry people because Dallas
gente ardida porque dallas se lleve bien
now gets along with Vitti, okay, they have a
ahora con vitti vale tenga una relación
cordial relationship that they have even followed each other on
cordial que incluso se han seguido en
Twitter. Hey, how nice and how proud
twitter oye qué bonito y qué orgulloso
I feel as a mutual friend of having you, of having
me siento como amigo en común de haberos
been the one to blame for
de haber de haber sido el culpable de
this, the truth is, of having been the one to
esto la verdad
blame for this, the truth is that I
de haber sido el culpable de esto la
saw, the truth is that well, I
verdad que vi la verdad que bien
say tomorrow we will read the forum
ya digo mañana vamos a leer el foro
from page 178 to where we
desde la página 178 hasta donde
get to, okay.
lleguemos vale